{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Application Development and Emerging Technologies",
    "Term": "Prefinals",
    "Title": "Software Review and Inspection",
    "LastModified": "21 November 2024",
    "Authors": [
      ""
    ],
    "References": [
      ""
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "This is a formalized peer review process for detecting and correcting defects or bugs in software artifacts.",
      "answer": "Software Inspection and Review",
      "choices": [
        "Software Inspection and Review",
        "Software Prototyping",
        "Software Quality Assurance",
        "Rawr"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Its objective is to help developers build quality into the software product.",
      "answer": "Software Inspection and Review",
      "choices": [
        "Software Inspection and Review",
        "Software Prototyping",
        "Software Quality Assurance",
        "Rawr"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "These are anything that have been documented and stored during the software development process such as requirements document, source code, user documentation, test plans, and test cases.",
      "answer": "Sofrtware Artifacts",
      "choices": [
        "Sofrtware Artifacts",
        "Software Bugs",
        "Software Errors",
        "Software Components"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This software inspection technique is developed by Michael Fagan. (Pag ito namali mo pa ewan ko nalang)",
      "answer": "Fagan Inspection Methodology",
      "choices": [
        "Fagan Inspection Methodology",
        "Structured Walkthrough",
        "Inspection Meeting",
        "Code Reviewing Techniques"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This software inspection technique identifies and removes errors in the software products and to identify any systematic defects in the processes that are used to create software products.",
      "answer": "Fagan Inspection Methodology",
      "choices": [
        "Fagan Inspection Methodology",
        "Structured Walkthrough",
        "Inspection Meeting",
        "Code Reviewing Techniques"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This software inspection technique requires that software artifacts be formally inspected by experts independent of the author.",
      "answer": "Fagan Inspection Methodology",
      "choices": [
        "Fagan Inspection Methodology",
        "Structured Walkthrough",
        "Inspection Meeting",
        "Code Reviewing Techniques"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This software inspection technique includes roles namely, moderator, author, reader, and tester.",
      "answer": "Fagan Inspection Methodology",
      "choices": [
        "Fagan Inspection Methodology",
        "Structured Walkthrough",
        "Inspection Meeting",
        "Code Reviewing Techniques"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This software inspection technique is a peer review in which the author of a deliverable, such as a document or source code, brings 1 or more reviewers through the deliverable.",
      "answer": "Structured Walkthrough",
      "choices": [
        "Fagan Inspection Methodology",
        "Structured Walkthrough",
        "Inspection Meeting",
        "Code Reviewing Techniques"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This software inspection technique's objective is to get feedback from the reviewers on the quality of the document or code and to familiarize the review audience with the authorâ€™s work.",
      "answer": "Structured Walkthrough",
      "choices": [
        "Fagan Inspection Methodology",
        "Structured Walkthrough",
        "Inspection Meeting",
        "Code Reviewing Techniques"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This software inspection technique includes several roles, namely, the review leader, author, scribe, and the review audience.",
      "answer": "Structured Walkthrough",
      "choices": [
        "Fagan Inspection Methodology",
        "Structured Walkthrough",
        "Inspection Meeting",
        "Code Reviewing Techniques"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which inspector role leads the inspection team and takes care of logistics?",
      "answer": "Moderator",
      "choices": [
        "Moderator",
        "Author",
        "Reader",
        "Tester"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which inspector role is the creator of the software artifacts under inspection?",
      "answer": "Author",
      "choices": [
        "Moderator",
        "Author",
        "Reader",
        "Tester"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which inspector role actively answers all the questions regarding the artifacts during the inspection meeting?",
      "answer": "Author",
      "choices": [
        "Moderator",
        "Author",
        "Reader",
        "Tester"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which inspector role is responsible for fixing identified defects and bugs in the artifacts?",
      "answer": "Author",
      "choices": [
        "Moderator",
        "Author",
        "Reader",
        "Tester"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which inspector role is an experienced peer who can be a subject matter expert on the software artifacts under inspection?",
      "answer": "Reader",
      "choices": [
        "Moderator",
        "Author",
        "Reader",
        "Tester"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which inspector role is responsible for writing and executing test cases for the software module or product?",
      "answer": "Tester",
      "choices": [
        "Moderator",
        "Author",
        "Reader",
        "Tester"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which inspector role is focused on how the product would be tested?",
      "answer": "Tester",
      "choices": [
        "Moderator",
        "Author",
        "Reader",
        "Tester"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which activity involves identifying the inspector and roles, along with arranging the meeting place and time?",
      "answer": "Planning",
      "choices": [
        "Planning",
        "Overview",
        "Preparation",
        "Inspection Meeting"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which activity involves briefing of participants on information of materials?",
      "answer": "Overview",
      "choices": [
        "Planning",
        "Overview",
        "Preparation",
        "Inspection Meeting"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which activity involves preparation for the meeting and reading through the deliverables?",
      "answer": "Preparation",
      "choices": [
        "Planning",
        "Overview",
        "Preparation",
        "Inspection Meeting"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which activity involves the moderator setting the time limit for inspection and recording and classifying defects?",
      "answer": "Inspection Meeting",
      "choices": [
        "Planning",
        "Overview",
        "Preparation",
        "Inspection Meeting"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which activity involves improving the development and inspection process along with making recommendation to the process improvement team?",
      "answer": "Process Improvement",
      "choices": [
        "Process Improvement",
        "Rework",
        "Follow-up",
        "Preparation"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which activity involves the author correcting the defects and carries out any necessary investigations?",
      "answer": "Rework",
      "choices": [
        "Process Improvement",
        "Rework",
        "Follow-up",
        "Preparation"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which activity involves the moderator verifying that the author has resolved the defects and investigations?",
      "answer": "Follow-up",
      "choices": [
        "Process Improvement",
        "Rework",
        "Follow-up",
        "Preparation"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which inspection type finds defects in the requirements and confirming if those are correct?",
      "answer": "Requirements",
      "choices": [
        "Requirements",
        "Design Inspection",
        "Code Inspection",
        "Test Plan Inspection"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which inspection type finds defects in the design and confirming if those are correct with respect to the requirements?",
      "answer": "Design Inspection",
      "choices": [
        "Requirements",
        "Design Inspection",
        "Code Inspection",
        "Test Plan Inspection"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which inspection type finds defects in the code and confirming if those are correct with respect to the design and requirements?",
      "answer": "Code Inspection",
      "choices": [
        "Requirements",
        "Design Inspection",
        "Code Inspection",
        "Test Plan Inspection"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fagan Inspection Methodology, which inspection type finds defects in the test cases or plan, and confirming if those can verify the design and requirements?",
      "answer": "Test Plan Inspection",
      "choices": [
        "Requirements",
        "Design Inspection",
        "Code Inspection",
        "Test Plan Inspection"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is an act of systematically convening with fellow programmers to check each otherâ€™s code for faults to ensure it meets quality standards.",
      "answer": "Code Reviewing Techniques",
      "choices": [
        "Code Reviewing Techniques",
        "Developer-Driven Code Review",
        "Tool-Driven Code Review",
        "Modern Code Review"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This Code Reviewing Technique uses automated code analysis techniques that can pick out problematic patterns within the source code.",
      "answer": "Tool-Driven Code Review",
      "choices": [
        "Code Reviewing Techniques",
        "Developer-Driven Code Review",
        "Tool-Driven Code Review",
        "Modern Code Review"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This Code Reviewing Technique states that the nature of the code problems that can be identified varies from 1 tool to another and depends to an extent on the nature of the underlying programming language.",
      "answer": "Tool-Driven Code Review",
      "choices": [
        "Code Reviewing Techniques",
        "Developer-Driven Code Review",
        "Tool-Driven Code Review",
        "Modern Code Review"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This Code Reviewing Technique states that automated tools are especially good at identifying problems that are relatively localized to a single method or class.",
      "answer": "Tool-Driven Code Review",
      "choices": [
        "Code Reviewing Techniques",
        "Developer-Driven Code Review",
        "Tool-Driven Code Review",
        "Modern Code Review"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This Code Reviewing Technique is where the developers themselves review code to pick out problems.",
      "answer": "Developer-Driven Code Review",
      "choices": [
        "Code Reviewing Techniques",
        "Developer-Driven Code Review",
        "Tool-Driven Code Review",
        "Modern Code Review"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This Code Reviewing Technique is where reviewers manually assess codes before deployment.",
      "answer": "Developer-Driven Code Review",
      "choices": [
        "Code Reviewing Techniques",
        "Developer-Driven Code Review",
        "Tool-Driven Code Review",
        "Modern Code Review"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This Code Reviewing Technique is usually a 2-step process where the developers have to understand the program first so that they can form an opinion of its implementation and design.",
      "answer": "Developer-Driven Code Review",
      "choices": [
        "Code Reviewing Techniques",
        "Developer-Driven Code Review",
        "Tool-Driven Code Review",
        "Modern Code Review"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a lightweight variant of code inspections because it doesnâ€™t rely on face-to-face meetings.",
      "answer": "Modern Code Review",
      "choices": [
        "Code Reviewing Techniques",
        "Developer-Driven Code Review",
        "Tool-Driven Code Review",
        "Modern Code Review"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This Modern Code Review technique uses Google Gerrit or Microsoft CodeFlow.",
      "answer": "Tool-Driven Code Review",
      "choices": [
        "Code Reviewing Techniques",
        "Developer-Driven Code Review",
        "Tool-Driven Code Review",
        "Modern Code Review"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a central file storage location used by version control systems to store multiple versions of files that can be accessed by multiple users.",
      "answer": "Repository",
      "choices": [
        "Repository",
        "Pull-Based Development",
        "Code Reviewing Tools",
        "Pull Requests"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This Modern Code Review technique doesn't use code reviewing tools and revolves around a mechanism known as a pull request.",
      "answer": "Pull-Based Development",
      "choices": [
        "Repository",
        "Pull-Based Development",
        "Code Reviewing Tools",
        "Pull Requests"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    }
  ]
}